continue to speak about auto. Global EV
giant Tesla is reportedly in early talks
with Bajage Alliance and ICICI Lombard
for potential car insurance tie-ups in
India. While discussions remain
preliminary and non-exclusive, sources
say that Aqua has emerged as Tesla's
preferred insurer. My colleague Agni
brings us the exclusive details. Agni
>> Tesla might have entered India but the
bigger question that people are asking
are who will be the insurance provider
for the company. Sources tell us that
Bajage Alliance and ICIC Lombard are hot
in the race to get into tie-ups with
Tesla for insurance in their India
vehicles. Now Bajage Alliance and ICIC
Lombard are in early discussions with
Tesla at this point and no terms have
been finalized yet. sources tell us that
the firms are pitching for non-exclusive
tie-ups with Tesla and Tesla sources are
also telling us that the decision will
ultimately depend on the insurance
department working out of the company's
Hong Kong or Singapore offices. Now
remember to get a license in India to
get an insurance service provider in
India. Tesla needs to get a motor
insurance service provider license from
the IRDI that will take another few
months is what the sources are telling
us and only then will they be able to do
a proper tie-up with an insurance
provider. We have reached out to Bajaz
Alliance and ICICI Lombard for their
comments on the story and this is a
developing point. So do stay tuned as we
bring you more updates.
[Music]